<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no" ?>
<examples>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGRE R. R. MARTIN</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Why is it that when one man builds a wall, the next man immediately needs to know what's on the other side?
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGRE R. R. MARTIN</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                My old grandmother always used to say, Summer friends will melt away like summer snows, but winter friends are friends forever.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGRE R. R. MARTIN</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Night gathers, and now my watch begins. It shall not end until my death. I shall take no wife, hold no
                lands, father no children. I shall wear no crowns and win no glory. I shall live and die at my post.
                I am the sword in the darkness. I am the watcher on the walls. I am the fire that burns against cold,
                the light that brings the dawn, the horn that wakes the sleepers, the shield that guards the realms of men.
                I pledge my life and honor to the Night's Watch, for this night and all the nights to come.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGRE R. R. MARTIN</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                You know nothing, Jon Snow.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGRE R. R. MARTIN</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                A cold wind was blowing from the north, and it made the trees rustle like living things.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGRE R. R. MARTIN</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                History is a wheel, for the nature of man is fundamentally unchanging. What has happened before will perforce happen again.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGRE R. R. MARTIN</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                I admire Tolkien greatly. His books had enormous influence on me. And the trope that he sort of
                established—the idea of the Dark Lord and his Evil Minions—in the hands of lesser writers over
                the years and decades has not served the genre well. It has been beaten to death. The battle of
                good and evil is a great subject for any book and certainly for a fantasy book, but I think ultimately
                the battle between good and evil is weighed within the individual human heart and not necessarily
                between an army of people dressed in white and an army of people dressed in black. When I look at the
                world, I see that most real living breathing human beings are grey.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGRE R. R. MARTIN</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Noseless and Handless, the Lannister Boys.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGRE R. R. MARTIN</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                The great thing about reading is that it broadens your life
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGRE R. R. MARTIN</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Aemon’s blind white eyes came open. “Egg?” he said, as the rain streamed down his cheeks. “Egg, I dreamed that I was old.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGRE R. R. MARTIN</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                A day will come when you think yourself safe and happy, and suddenly your joy will turn to ashes in your mouth, and you'll know the debt is paid.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGRE R. R. MARTIN</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Be careful you don't cut yourself. The edges are sharp enough to shave with.'
                'Girls don't shave', Arya said.
                'Maybe they should. Have you ever seen the septa's legs?
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGRE R. R. MARTIN</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                You are the blood of the dragon. You can make a hat.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGRE R. R. MARTIN</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Jon:'What are you doing up there? Why aren't you at the feast?'
                Tyrion: 'Too hot, too noisy, and I'd drunk too much wine', the dwarf told him.
                'I learned long ago that it is considered rude to vomit on your brother.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGRE R. R. MARTIN</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                You make us look bad', complained Toad.
                'You looked bad before I ever met you', Jon told him.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGRE R. R. MARTIN</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Hodor," said Hodor.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGRE R. R. MARTIN</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Soon comes the cold, and the night that never ends.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGRE R. R. MARTIN</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                And all was black and still, and black and cold, and black and dead, and black.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGRE R. R. MARTIN</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                I wish I was home", She said miserably.
                She tried so hard to be brave,
                to be fierce as a wolverine and all,
                but some times she felt she was a little girl after all.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGRE R. R. MARTIN</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Jaime smiled knowingly. Men will read all sorts of things into a knowing smile if you let them.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGRE R. R. MARTIN</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                We were talking about the prince,' Sansa said, her voice soft as a kiss.
                Arya knew which prince she meant: Joffrey, of course. The tall, handsome one.
                Sansa got to sit with him at the feast. Arya had to sit with the little fat one. Naturally.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGRE R. R. MARTIN</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                This is not Winterfell', he told him as he cut his meat with fork and dagger. 'On the Wall, a man gets
                only what he earns. You're no ranger, Jon, only a green boy with the smell of summer still on you.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGRE R. R. MARTIN</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Who do you think our champion will be today? Have you seen Mace Tyrell's boy? The Knight of Flowers,
                they call him. Now there's a son any man would be proud to own to. Last tourney, he dumped the Kingslayer
                on his golden rump, you ought to have seen the look on Cersei's face. I laughed till my sides hurt.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGRE R. R. MARTIN</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                You mistake patience for forbearance.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGRE R. R. MARTIN</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                That's one way we differ, Jaime and I. He's taller as well, you may have noticed.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGRE R. R. MARTIN</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                The day will come when you need them to respect you, even fear you a little. Laughter is poison to fear.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGRE R. R. MARTIN</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                I wonder what the High Septon would have to say about the sanctity of oaths sworn while dead drunk,
                chained to a wall, with a sword pressed to your chest?
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGRE R. R. MARTIN</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Lord Snow wants to take my place now.' He sneered. 'I'd have an easier time teaching a wolf to juggle
                than you will training this aurochs.'
                'I'll take that wager, Ser Alliser', Jon said. 'I'd love to see Ghost juggle.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGRE R. R. MARTIN</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                His cloak was his crowning glory; sable, thick and black and soft as sin.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGRE R. R. MARTIN</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                His dagger was out, poised at her throat. “Sing, little bird. Sing for your little life.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGRE R. R. MARTIN</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                That boy had wanted to be Ser Arthur Dayne, but someplace along the way he had become the Smiling Knight instead.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGRE R. R. MARTIN</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                There is only one god, death and there is only one thing you say to him, not today.
                -Syrio Forell
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGRE R. R. MARTIN</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                The hard truths are the ones to hold tight. - Old Bear
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGRE R. R. MARTIN</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                So the wolfling is leaving his den to play among the lions," he said in a voice of quiet satisfaction.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGE ORWELL</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Perhaps one did not want to be loved so much as to be understood.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGE ORWELL</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Who controls the past controls the future. Who controls the present controls the past.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGE ORWELL</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                In a time of deceit telling the truth is a revolutionary act.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGE ORWELL</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                War is peace.
                Freedom is slavery.
                Ignorance is strength.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGE ORWELL</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                All animals are equal, but some animals are more equal than others.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGE ORWELL</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Every generation imagines itself to be more intelligent than the one that went before it,
                and wiser than the one that comes after it.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGE ORWELL</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                The best books... are those that tell you what you know already.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGE ORWELL</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                The creatures outside looked from pig to man, and from man to pig, and from pig to man again;
                but already it was impossible to say which was which.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGE ORWELL</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                If you want to keep a secret, you must also hide it from yourself.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGE ORWELL</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                The most effective way to destroy people is to deny and obliterate their own understanding of their history.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGE ORWELL</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                It was a bright cold day in April, and the clocks were striking thirteen.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGE ORWELL</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                If you want a picture of the future, imagine a boot stamping on a human face—for ever.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGE ORWELL</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                We shall meet in the place where there is no darkness.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGE ORWELL</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                But if thought corrupts language, language can also corrupt thought.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGE ORWELL</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Political language is designed to make lies sound truthful and murder respectable, and to give an
                appearance of solidity to pure wind.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGE ORWELL</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Doublethink means the power of holding two contradictory beliefs in one's mind simultaneously,
                and accepting both of them.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGE ORWELL</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                If liberty means anything at all, it means the right to tell people what they do not want to hear.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGE ORWELL</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Until they become conscious they will never rebel, and until after they have rebelled
                they cannot become conscious.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGE ORWELL</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Now I will tell you the answer to my question. It is this. The Party seeks power entirely for its own
                sake. We are not interested in the good of others; we are interested solely in power, pure power.
                What pure power means you will understand presently. We are different from the oligarchies of the past
                in that we know what we are doing. All the others, even those who resembled ourselves, were cowards and
                hypocrites. The German Nazis and the Russian Communists came very close to us in their methods, but they
                never had the courage to recognize their own motives. They pretended, perhaps they even believed, that
                they had seized power unwillingly and for a limited time, and that just around the corner there lay a
                paradise where human beings would be free and equal. We are not like that. We know that no one ever
                seizes power with the intention of relinquishing it. Power is not a means; it is an end. One does not
                establish a dictatorship in order to safeguard a revolution; one makes the revolution in order to
                establish the dictatorship. The object of persecution is persecution. The object of torture is torture.
                The object of power is power. Now you begin to understand me.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGE ORWELL</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Perhaps a lunatic was simply a minority of one.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGE ORWELL</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                If you loved someone, you loved him, and when you had nothing else to give, you still gave him love.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGE ORWELL</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                In the face of pain there are no heroes.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGE ORWELL</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Power is in tearing human minds to pieces and putting them together again in new shapes of your own choosing.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGE ORWELL</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Writing a book is a horrible, exhausting struggle, like a long bout with some painful illness.
                One would never undertake such a thing if one were not driven on by some demon whom one can neither
                resist nor understand.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGE ORWELL</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Being in a minority, even in a minority of one, did not make you mad. There was truth and there was
                untruth, and if you clung to the truth even against the whole world, you were not mad.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGE ORWELL</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                The essence of being human is that one does not seek perfection.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGE ORWELL</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Big Brother is Watching You.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGE ORWELL</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                It's a beautiful thing, the destruction of words.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGE ORWELL</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Freedom is the freedom to say that two plus two make four. If that is granted, all else follows.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGE ORWELL</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                So the wolfling is leaving his den to play among the lions," he said in a voice of quiet satisfaction.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>GEORGE ORWELL</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                The choice for mankind lies between freedom and happiness and for the great bulk of mankind,
                happiness is better.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                You speak an infinite deal of nothing.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                These violent delights have violent ends
                And in their triump die, like fire and powder
                Which, as they kiss, consume
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                To die, to sleep -
                To sleep, perchance to dream - ay, there's the rub,
                For in this sleep of death what dreams may come
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Let me not to the marriage of true minds
                Admit impediments. Love is not love
                Which alters when it alteration finds,
                Or bends with the remover to remove.
                O no, it is an ever-fixed mark
                That looks on tempests and is never shaken;
                It is the star to every wand'ring barque,
                Whose worth's unknown, although his height be taken.
                Love's not Time's fool, though rosy lips and cheeks
                Within his bending sickle's compass come;
                Love alters not with his brief hours and weeks,
                But bears it out even to the edge of doom.
                If this be error and upon me proved,
                I never writ, nor no man ever loved.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                With mirth and laughter let old wrinkles come.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Shall I compare thee to a summer's day?
                Thou art more lovely and more temperate:
                Rough winds do shake the darling buds of May,
                And summer's lease hath all too short a date:
                Sometimes too hot the eye of heaven shines,
                And too often is his gold complexion dimm'd:
                And every fair from fair sometimes declines,
                By chance or natures changing course untrimm'd;
                By thy eternal summer shall not fade,
                Nor lose possession of that fair thou owest;
                Nor shall Death brag thou wander'st in his shade,
                When in eternal lines to time thou growest:
                So long as men can breathe or eyes can see,
                So long lives this and this gives life to thee.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Conscience doth make cowards of us all.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Et tu, Brute?
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Wisely and slow; they stumble that run fast.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                O serpent heart hid with a flowering face!
                Did ever a dragon keep so fair a cave?
                Beautiful tyrant, feind angelical, dove feather raven, wolvish-ravening lamb! Despised substance of
                devinest show, just opposite to what thou justly seemest - A dammed saint, an honourable villain!
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Some are born great, others achieve greatness.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Sweets to the sweet.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Lord Polonius: What do you read, my lord?
                Hamlet: Words, words, words.
                Lord Polonius: What is the matter, my lord?
                Hamlet: Between who?
                Lord Polonius: I mean, the matter that you read, my lord.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Some Cupid kills with arrows, some with traps.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Better a witty fool, than a foolish wit.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Are you sure/That we are awake? It seems to me/That yet we sleep, we dream
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                All's well that ends well.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                This goodly frame, the earth, seems to me a sterile promontory, this most excellent canopy, the air,
                look you, this brave o'erhanging firmament, this majestical roof fretted with golden fire, why, it
                appears no other thing to me than a foul and pestilent congregation of vapours. What a piece of work is
                a man! how noble in reason! how infinite in faculty! in form and moving how express and admirable!
                in action how like an angel! in apprehension how like a god! the beauty of the world! the paragon of
                animals! And yet, to me, what is this quintessence of dust?
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                All causes shall give way: I am in blood
                Stepp’d in so far that, should I wade no more,
                Returning were as tedious as go o’er.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                I love you with so much of my heart that none is left to protest.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Good name in man and woman, dear my lord,
                Is the immediate jewel of their souls:
                Who steals my purse steals trash; ’tis something, nothing;
                ’twas mine, ’tis his, and has been slave to thousands;
                But he that filches from me my good name
                Robs me of that which not enriches him,
                And makes me poor indeed.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Eye of newt, and toe of frog,
                Wool of bat, and tongue of dog,
                Adder's fork, and blind-worm's sting,
                Lizard's leg, and owlet's wing,—
                For a charm of powerful trouble,
                Like a hell-broth boil and bubble.
                Double, double toil and trouble;
                Fire burn, and caldron bubble.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Thou art a very ragged Wart.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Sweet are the uses of adversity
                Which, like the toad, ugly and venomous,
                Wears yet a precious jewel in his head.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                The Play's the Thing, wherein I'll catch the conscience of the King.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                The fault, dear Brutus, is not in our stars/ But in ourselves.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                Love is not love which alters when it alteration finds.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                I have no spur
                To prick the sides of my intent, but only
                Vaulting ambition, which o'erleaps itself
                And falls on the other.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
    <QUOTE>
        <AUTHOR>WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE</AUTHOR>
        <TEXT>
            <BODY>
                And therefore, — since I cannot prove a lover,
                To entertain these fair well-spoken days, —
                I am determined to prove a villain,
                And hate the idle pleasures of these days.
            </BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </QUOTE>
</examples>
